瑞秋  你知道怀孕的时候...
Rach, listen. Did you know that during pregnancy...
你的手指会肿成两倍粗
...your fingers swell up to twice their size
而且再也不会消了吗
and never go back?
天啊  让我看看
Oh, my God! Let me see that.
你每次都会上当
You fall for it every time.
我把我的旧孕妇装拿来给你
Hey! I brought you my old maternity clothes.
菲比  你真是太贴心了
Oh, Pheebs, that's so sweet.
好可爱哦  是啊
Oh, those are so cute!  Yes.
你看  宝宝越长越大 它们也会跟着撑开来
Look. See how they expand as the baby grows?
宝宝出生后
And then after the baby's born
可以穿它去偷西瓜
they're great for shoplifting melons.
太好了  你们都在  感恩节  明天四点
Good, you're all here. Okay. Thanksgiving, tomorrow, 4:00.
你猜我邀请了谁
Guess who I invited?
还记得高中同学威尔·卡佛特吗
Remember Will Culvert from high school?
不记得了  他跟罗斯同班
No.  He was in Ross' class.
他是军乐队的  有点胖
Marching band, was kind of overweight.
他是个大胖子
Really overweight.
我属于他的苗条朋友
I was his thin friend.
我不记得他了
I don't remember him.
你确定你说的不是你假想的男朋友吗
Are you sure you're not talking about your imaginary boyfriend?
不  那是贾拉德
No, that was Jared.
我好久没有想起他了
Haven't thought about him in a long time.
威尔来城里出差
Anyway, Will's here on business,
他没地方可去  所以我邀请他过来
and he didn't have a place to go, so I invited him here.
那很好啊  他减肥成功了
That's nice.  Oh, he's lost a bunch of weight.
他看起来很不错  他真的是帅呆了
He looks good. Okay, I mean really gorgeous.
我还爱着钱德勒
I still love Chandler.
偶尔提一次不会要你的命
Wouldn't hurt you to say it once in a while.
先说好了  今年我不烤火鸡
Just so you know, I'm not gonna make a turkey this year...
什么  菲比不吃火鸡
What?  Phoebe doesn't eat turkey.
菲比  火鸡是漂亮聪明的动物
Phoebe!  Turkeys are beautiful, intelligent animals.
不是的  它们既丑又蠢  但很好吃
No, they're not! They're ugly and stupid and delicious!
不只是菲比  威尔还在节食
It's not just Phoebe.Will's still on a diet,
钱德勒不吃感恩节食物...
Chandler doesn't eat Thanksgiving food...
瑞秋对家禽类反胃  是吗
Rachel's having her aversion to poultry.  She is?
对  记得吗  那天你吃烤鸡时
Yeah. Remember? I had to leave the other day
我不得不走开
when you had that roast chicken.
我还以为是因为我把烧鸡套在手上
Yeah. I thought that was because I put the whole thing on my hand
让它在桌子上走路
and made it walk across the table.
为了三个人做一只火鸡太不划算了
It's not worth it to make a whole turkey for just three people.
那真的很费功夫
It's a lot of work.
但感恩节一定要吃火鸡啊
But you gotta have turkey on Thanksgiving!
感恩节不吃火鸡
I mean, Thanksgiving with no turkey is like
就像国庆日不吃苹果派
Fourth of July with no apple pie.
或是星期五不吃两个披萨
Or Friday with no two pizzas.
如果真的对你那么重要的话我就做
Fine, if it means that much to you.
但到时候一定会剩下很多
But there's gonna be a ton left over.
不  我发誓我会把整只火鸡吃完
No, there won't. I promise I will finish that turkey.
你是说你可以一次吃掉
You're telling me you can eat almost
一整只火鸡
an entire turkey in one sitting?
没错  因为我是崔比亚尼家的人
That's right. Because I'm a Tribbiani!
这是我们的专长
This is what we do.
我们不是伟大的思想家或世界领袖...
We may not be great thinkers or world leaders...
我们书念得不多  跑得不快
...we don't read a lot or run fast,
但我们绝对是大胃王
but damn it, we can eat!
《老友记》  第八季  第9集  谣言
Friends S08E09 The One With The Rumor
第四次长传  第三次18码
Four wide receivers. On third and 18.
明年桌边会坐一个宝宝
Isn't it weird to think about how next year there this time
感觉很奇怪吧
there will be a baby at the table?
我是指瑞秋的孩子
Rachel's.
但我很高兴知道你的真实想法
But good to know where you're at.
感恩节快乐  你也是
Happy Thanksgiving.  You too!
需要我帮忙吗  好啊
Anything I can do to help?  Actually there is.
通常钱德勒会帮忙 但他看球赛看得正入迷
Chandler usually helps me with this, but he's really into the game
我不想打扰他
so I don't want to bother him.
麻烦你帮忙折餐巾吧  没问题
Could you help me to fold these napkins?  Sure.
我要去对面看看地瓜泥好了没  好
I'm gonna go across the hall to check on the yams.  Okay.
不  亲爱的  不是那样折
No, sweetie. No, not like that.
我们不是在办农场舞会
We're not at a barn dance.
要把它们折成天鹅的形状
You've gotta fold them like swans.
我在圣诞节时教过你  记得吗
Like I showed you at Christmas. Remember?
记得  一切历历在目
Yeah, it all just came screaming back to me.
球赛好看吗  我不知道
So how's the game?  I have no idea.
什么  我假装看球赛
What?  Yeah, I'm just pretending to watch the game
那样子就不必帮忙
...so I don't have to help out with stuff.
我不敢相信
I don't believe you!
这招太高明了
That is brilliant!
莫妮卡没发觉吗  对
And Monica has no idea?  No.
偶尔我会对着电视大叫
Every once and a while, I just scream stuff at the TV.
怎么回事
Hey! What? Aw! Hey!
你的球队赢了吗  安德森刚刚又得分了
Your team winning, hon?  Yeah. Anderson just scored again.
根本就没有安德森这号人物
There is no Anderson.
我也想如法炮制  莫妮卡
I wanna get in on this. Hey, Mon?
看来我没办法帮你了
I don't think I can help you after all.
我不知道今天会播这场球赛
I didn't realize this game was on.
没听说你喜欢橄榄球  我平时不喜欢
I don't know you like football.  Normally, I don't.
但今天是绿湾队在比赛
But, you know, Green Bay is playing.
你喜欢绿湾队  那是我最喜欢的海湾
You like Green Bay?  It's only my favorite bay.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
谢谢  威尔  我很高兴你能来
Thanks. Will, I'm so glad that you came.
你看起来帅呆了  你一定减掉了
You look great. You must've lost like...
150磅
150 pounds.
我会是赛百味三明治广告的下一号人选
I'll be on one of those Subway sandwich commercials.
是派  零脂肪  无糖  也没有奶
A pie!  It's no fat, it's no sugar, it's no dairy.
一点都不好吃  丢了吧
It's no good. Throw it out.
我来介绍你们认识
You wanna meet some people.
这是我丈夫钱德勒  这是威尔
This is my husband, Chandler. Chandler, this is Will.
我很想跟你握手  但我忙着看球赛
Oh, hey. I'd shake your hand but I'm really into the game.
而且如果我们两个不站在一起
Plus, I think it'd be better for my ego
我的自尊就不会那么受伤
if we didn't stand right next to each other.
这是菲比
This is Phoebe.
干得好
Well done.
你要帮我吗  好
Wanna give me a hand?  Sure.
莫妮卡  我真的觉得你很漂亮
Monica, I can't get over how great you look. You look stunning.
你也很帅  你身材真棒
You look incredible too. You're so fit.
虽说我在看球赛  但我没聋
I'm watching the game, but I'm not deaf.
我一直想告诉你  罗斯也会来
I meant to tell you, Ross is coming.
太棒了  我喜欢罗斯
Ross is coming. Great, I love Ross.
很好  瑞秋·格林也会来
Good. And Rachel Greene too.
有问题吗  没有  没关系的
Is there a problem?  No. It's okay.
只是...天啊  我恨她
It's just... God, I hated her.
什么  我恨她
What?  Yeah. I hated her.
高中时她对我很差劲
She was horrible to me in high school.
但那是很久以前的事了
But hey, that was a long time ago.
我现在一切都好  或许再见到她会很有趣
I'm in a good place. Might be fun to see her again.
你有蛋糕或饼干什么的吗
Got any cakes or cookies or something?
不行  威尔  不行
No, Will! No!
我们很久没大叫了  或许我们该叫一下
It's been a while since we screamed. Maybe we should.
好吧  不要啊  加油
Oh, okay. No!  Come on!
该死的裁判  下地狱去吧
Damn you, ref! You burn in hell!
你这是要干嘛
What are you doing?
你还得吃掉一整只火鸡
You gotta save room, you've got almost an entire turkey to eat.
让我跟你解释一下人体的运作原理
Let me explain to you how the human body works.
我得先让我的胃暖暖身
I have to warm up my stomach first.
吃薯片像是在做拉筋运动  好吧
Eating chips is like stretching.  Okay.
别担心  崔比亚尼永远吃不饱
Don't worry, Tribbianis never get full.
我知道你的意思
I actually know what you're talking about.
我要告诉你一件事
I'm here to tell you something, friend.
你可以吃个不停  但你无法填满内心的空虚
You can eat and eat, but nothing will ever fill that void.
这家伙到底是谁
Who the hell is this guy?
他是我们的高中同学威尔  他是乔伊
This is Will, from high school. This is Joey.
威尔  罗斯
Will!  Ross!
你来了
Hey, you came!
天啊  你看起来棒极了  大帅哥
Man, you look incredible! Hot stuff!
大帅哥  很高兴能见到你
Hot stuff ?  It's good to see you, man.
我也是  你是做哪一行的
Yeah. You too. So, what are you up to?
我是期货经纪人  听起来很有趣
I'm a commodities broker.  Really? That sounds interesting.
才怪
Yeah, it's not.
但我现在既有钱  身材又好
But I'm rich and thin.
自从兰西戴维斯的毕业派对之后我就没有见过你
I haven't seen you since Lance Davis' graduation party.
那一晚真的很疯狂
That was such a fun night.
如果我们都有被邀请就好了 但还是很疯狂
Would've been good if we had gotten in, but still real fun.
那时我们逊毙了
We were lame back then.
你还记得我们当时多迷恐龙吗
Do you remember how into dinosaurs we were?
对  你是做哪一行的
Yeah.  So, what do you do now?
你要在城里待多久
So how long are you in town?
亲爱的  太好了
Hey, sweetie. Oh, good.
瑞秋·格林
Rachel Greene.
对了  你没事吧
Oh, that's right. Are you gonna be okay?
我没事  只是...
Oh, I'll be fine. It's just...
天啊  罗斯  我恨她
God, I hate her, Ross! I hate her!
高中是很久以前的事了
Will, high school was a long time ago.
看看她拿着地瓜泥站在那里的样子
Look at her standing there with those yams.
我的两个死对头
My two greatest enemies, Ross:
瑞秋·格林跟碳水化合物
Rachel Greene and complex carbohydrates.
天啊  莫妮卡  那是谁
Oh, my God. Monica, who is that?
他是我们的高中同学威尔
That's Will, from high school.
我不记得他了
Oh! I do not remember him.
他真的越来越性感了
Wow, really got that sexy smoldering thing going on.
天啊  看他盯着我瞧的样子
Oh, my God. Look at the way he's just staring at me.
他好像想用唇语跟我说话  但看不出说的什么
He's trying to mouth something to me, but I can't make it out.
我恨你
I hate you!
好了  晚餐准备好了  好吧
Okay, dinner's ready!  Okay!
真的很精彩  谁赢了
Solid effort. Solid effort.  Oh, so who won?
绿湾队  底特律队
Green Bay.  Detroit.
什么  技术上来说狮队赢了
What?  The Lions technically won.
但在士气方面是绿湾美人鱼队赢了
But it was a moral victory for the Green Bay Mermen.
你是威尔吧  对
Hi! Will, right?  Right.
我是瑞秋·格林
Right, hi. I'm Rachel Greene.
我记得你  真的吗  你真好
Oh, I remember you.  Really? aren't you sweet?
我得告诉你  我真的很难记得你的样子
I gotta tell you though, I'm having the hardest time placing you.
等一下  我想我记得你
Hang on! I think I remember you.
我们...
Did we...
我们在兰西戴维斯的毕业派对上鬼混过吗
Did we fool around at Lance Davis' graduation party?
你真是不可思议  谢谢你
You are unbelievable.  Thank you.
瑞秋  你坐这边  威尔  你坐到那边去
Rachel? Why don't you sit here? And Will, you sit way over there.
就那样
That's it?
即使没有人帮我  我也可以吃掉它
Even if nobody helps me, I can eat that.
没问题  至少给我一点挑战
No problem. At least give me a challenge.
这是钱德勒的鸡肉
This is Chandler's chicken.
这才是火鸡
This is the turkey.
这有多大
How big is that?
大约19磅
About 19 pounds.
它跟我刚出生时差不多大
It's like me when I was born.
谁想吃地瓜泥  威尔
Alright. Who would like some yams? Will?
你喜欢那样做  对吧
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
什么  拜托把鸡肉...
What? Oh, you know what, can we please keep the chicken...
跟火鸡放到另一边去
...and the turkey and everything on the other side of the table?
那个味道真的恶心  太典型了
The smell is just...  Typical.
什么  我说那太典型了
I'm sorry. What?  I said it was typical.
瑞秋·格林的典型作风
Typical of you. Rachel Green.
瑞秋女王在瑞秋王国想做什么就做什么
Queen Rachel does whatever she wants in Rachelland.
说真的  这家伙是谁
Seriously, who is this guy?
抱歉  你对我有意见吗
Sorry, do you have a problem with me?
我不知道  我有吗
I don't know. Do I? Do I?
我想你有
I think you do.
你在高中时对他有点恶劣
Apparently, You were a little mean to him in high school.
有点恶劣  你让我活在痛苦深渊
A little mean? You made my life miserable.
我不知道  抱歉
I had no idea. I'm sorry.
你应该抱歉  去他的
Well, you should be. Screw it.
把地瓜泥拿过来给我
Bring on the yams.
威尔  但你很努力在减肥
Will, but you worked so hard.
地瓜泥  好的
Yams!  Okay.
不论在高中时  我对你做了什么
Will, I just want to say that I'm real sorry
我都非常抱歉
for whatever I did to you in high school.
不只是我  我们组了一个社团
It wasn't just me. We had a club.
你们组了一个社团
You had a club?
没错  "我恨瑞秋·格林社"
That's right. The "I Hate Rachel Greene Club"!
天啊  你们全都聚在一起恨我吗
My god. So you all just joined together to hate me?
还有谁加入了那个社团  我跟罗斯
Who else was in this club?  Me and Ross.
你不必指我  她知道罗斯是谁
No need to point. She knows who Ross is.
你加入了"我恨瑞秋社"  没错
You were in an "I Hate Rachel" club?  Yes, he was.
不要
No, no.
还有谁参加了你们的社团
So who else was in this club?
那个来自泰国的交换学生
Actually, there was also that exchange student from Thailand
但我想他不知道那是怎么一回事
but I don't think he knew what it was.
罗斯  我们交往了两年...
So, Ross, we went out for two years...
你没有告诉我你参加过"我恨瑞秋社"
...and you never told me you were in an "I Hate Rachel Club"?
你跟她交往过  我们说好的
You went out with her? We had a pact.
那是高中的事了  又不是永久的约定
It was in high school. It's not like it was binding forever.
那为什么里面有"永远"这个字眼
Then why did it have the word eternity in it?
莫妮卡  你知道这件事吗
Monica? Did you know about this?
我发誓不知道
I swear I didn't.
所以你们才会常把房门锁上吗
Is that why you used to lock the bedroom door?
对  我得说我松了一口气
Yeah.  A little relieved, I gotta say.
听着  瑞秋  我很抱歉  好吗
Look, Rach, I'm sorry, okay?
那时我是个愚蠢的孩子
I was a stupid kid, okay?
我会加入社团是因为...  是一起成立
The only reason I joined...  Cofounded.
一起成立
Cofounded.
我一起成立那个社团是因为我那时疯狂地爱着你
Cofounded the club, was that I was insanely in love with you.
显然我处理得不够好
Obviously I didn't handle it very well.
但如果你仔细想想
If you think about it,
"我恨瑞秋社"其实是"我爱瑞秋社"
the "I Hate Rachel Club" was really the "I Love Rachel Club."
但它真的是"我恨瑞秋社"
Except that it was really the "I Hate Rachel Club."
难道你们就聚到一起说我的坏话吗
Okay. So you'd get together and like just say mean things about me?
不只是那样  没有没有
We did a little more than that.  No, no, no.
你们还做了什么
What else did you do?
我们散布一个谣言  什么谣言
We started a rumor.  What rumor?
快点  威尔  脱掉上衣  告诉我们
Come on, Will, just take off your shirt and tell us.
罗斯  那真的没什么
Ross?  It was no big deal.
我们说...
We said that...
那个谣言是...
The rumor was that...
你同时有男性跟女性的生殖器官
...you had both male and female reproductive parts.
什么  没错  我们说你爸妈
What?  That's right. We said your parents...
丢铜板决定把你当成女孩养大
...flipped a coin, decided to raise you as a girl,
但你还是有小鸡鸡
but you still had a hint of a penis.
天啊  那是你们编的
Oh, my God!  You started that?
你也听过  我们学校里每个人都听过
What? You heard that?  Everyone at our school heard it!
我的学校里每个人都听过
Everyone at my school heard it.
你就是那个长岛的双性啦啦队员
You were the hermaphrodite cheerleader from Long Island?
不
Oh, no!
现在我终于懂了
Oh my God! This is all making so much sense to me now!
所以亚当·卡特不想跟我约会
This is why Adam Can'ter wouldn't go out with me.
为什么比利·特雷特只想对这块区域下手
This is why Billy Tratt would just stay in this region!
比利·特雷特成了男同志
Actually, Billy Tratt is gay now,
所以那不是我们的错
so that one's not really our fault.
莫妮卡  你为什么不告诉我
Monica, how come you never told me this?
我想或许那是真的
I thought it might be true.
我担心你会大哭把它掏出来给我看
I was afraid that you were gonna cry and then show it to me.
乔伊别看了  那里面没有东西
Joey, stop staring! There's nothing there!
那不是真的
It's not true!
恐怕我需要证据
I'm afraid I'm gonna need proof.
你是我的珠穆朗玛峰
You are my Everest.
你不必吃完它
Joey, you don't have to finish that.
我必须吃完  不然接下来会怎样
Yes, I do. Otherwise, what's next?
今天我吃不完一只火鸡
Today I’m just a guy who can't finish a turkey,
明天我只能吃一半的三明治
but tomorrow I'm the guy who eats half a Powerbar,
把剩下的部分包起来放在冰箱  不行
...wrap it up and put it in the fridge? No!
我得去换条裤子
I just... I just gotta change my pants.
我在想什么  牛仔裤根本没有伸缩性
What was I thinking? Jeans have no give.
好了
Okay, okay.
你们看史恩·麦马洪在我的纪念册上写了什么
Listen to what Sean McMahon wrote in my yearbook senior year.
"亲爱的瑞秋  你真是个好人"
"Dear Rach, you're such a great person."
不是女孩  是"人"
Not girl, "person."
瑞秋  我觉得你太敏感了
Rach, I think you're reading a little too much into it.
"亲爱的瑞秋  你是个好人
"Dear Rach. You're a great person.
关于你有小鸡鸡的事我很遗憾"
Sorry about your teeny weenie."
你要我怎么做
What do you want me to do...
你要我打电话给全校的人
I want me to call everyone in the entire school
告诉他们那不是真的
and tell them it wasn't true?
对  可以顺便告诉他们我变瘦了吗
Yes.  Could you also tell them I'm skinny now?
还有我
Oh! Me too!
我不会打电话给任何人
Look, I won't call anybody.
那是很久以前的事了
It was a million years ago.
我不在乎那是多久之前的事了
I don't care how long ago it was.
你们告诉大家我是双性人
You told people that I was half and half!
我要说明一点
You know what? I just want to point out
在高中  我没做过任何伤害你的事
I never did anything to hurt you in high school.
那不完全是真的
That's not totally true.
什么  什么
What?  What?
你告诉大家罗斯
You did start that rumor about Ross...
跟50岁大的图书馆员亚特曼太太亲热
...making out with Mrs. Altmann, our 50yearold librarian.
你怎么知道那件事
How did you know that?
那是真的  不是
It's true?  No.
是真的  我看到你们躲在书卡柜的后面
Yes, it is. I saw you guys going at it behind the card catalog.
亚特曼太太
Mrs. Altmann?
她在塔塔卡奇奇回泰国前一晚
She also made out with TaTakaKiKek
也跟他亲热了
the night before he went back to Thailand.
抱歉  你高中的时候
I'm sorry. When you were in high school
跟50岁的女人亲热过
you made out with a 50yearold woman?
她看起来不像50岁
Hey, she didn't look 50!
她看起来像16岁吗
Did she look 16?
事实上纪念册里有她的照片
There's a picture of her in the yearbook actually.
哇  她不太上相
Wow.  She didn't photograph well!
大概是因为大半辈子都坐着当油画模特
She probably wasn't familiar with the process
她不太熟悉照相的方法技巧
having spent most of her life sitting for oil paintings.
这件事是怎么发生的
How did this happen?
她勾引你去吃早鸟晚餐吗
Did she lure you to an earlybird dinner?
有一天下午我在图书馆里看书看到很晚
I was working late in the library one afternoon.
馆里只有我们两个人
It was just the two of us.
她需要人帮忙玩填字游戏
She needed some help with her word jumble.
事情很自然就发生了
And one thing led to another.
我得告诉你们
If you must know,
安妮塔非常仁慈温柔
Anita was very gentle and tender.
希望她能得到安息
May she rest in peace.
她不是柱着拐杖走路吗
Did't she walk with a cane?
只有在天气潮湿的时候
Only when it was damp!
我不敢相信你把这件事告诉了大家
I can't believe you told people about this.
大家都知道吗
Everybody knew?
好了  我要重回社团  耶
You know what? I'm back in the club!  Yeah!
我要加入  菲比
I wanna join!  Phoebe?
抱歉  我从来没有加入过社团
I'm sorry, but I never got to be in a club.
我没有念过高中
I didn't go to high school.
但我们三个可以躲在垃圾箱后面学法文
But three of us would meet behind a dumpster to learn French.
你好
Bonjour.
好吧  你们可以继续那个愚蠢的小社团
Fine, you can have your stupid, little club.
但我要说  你对我做的事
but I would just like to say is what you did to me
比我对你做的事更糟糕
is way worse than what I did to you!
你说我有小鸡鸡  对
You gave me a teeny weenie.  Yeah!
听我说
Alright, listen.
你真的太傻了  瑞秋  即使有那个谣言
You're just being silly. Rachel, even with that rumor...
你还是学校里最受欢迎的女生之一
...you were one of the most popular girls in school.
大家都希望能跟你一样
Everyone wanted to be like you.
有个女孩太想变得跟你一样
One girl wanted to be like you so much,
她甚至往裤档里塞棒条糖
she stuffed her pants with a Tootsie Roll.
罗斯  要不是她的谣言
And Ross, if it weren't for Rachel's rumor,
学校里没有人会知道你是谁
no one in high school would've even known who you were.
是她让你成名
She put you on the map.
以老女人的情人成名
As a romancer of the elderly.
可以看得出来
Mrs. Altman was the kind of woman
亚特曼太太年轻的时候很漂亮
you could tell she used to be pretty.
她的眼睛光芒不减当年
The eyes did still sparkle.
这都是陈年往事了
Guys, this stuff is so way in the past.
从那之后你们也经历过很多事
You've been through so much since then.
你们未来的生活
And right now, you got so much more important stuff
还有许多更重要的事
going on in your life.
你们就不能释怀吗
Can't you just let this go?
她说得对  我们的孩子快出生了
She's right.  Yeah, I mean. We are having a baby together.
等一下
Hold on.
你让她怀孕了  对
You got her pregnant?  Yeah.
你们要结婚了  不
Are you getting married?  No.
你搞大她的肚子  但却不娶她  兄弟
So you knocked her up but you're not gonna marry her. Dude.
有人要来吗  好吧
Anybody?  Okay.
跟我想像中的感觉完全一样
It's exactly how I imagined it would be.
好吧  火鸡在哪里
All right, where's that turkey?
那是我的孕妇裤
Joey, those are my maternity pants!
不  这是我的感恩节裤
No, these are my Thanksgiving pants!
好了  我吃完了
Well, that's it. I'm done.
留下了鸡肉汗
Here come the meat sweats.
乔伊  我们非常以你为荣
Well, Joey, we're all very proud of you.
我相信总统随时会致来贺电
I believe we can expect a call from the president any moment now.
有什么我们可以帮忙的吗
Anything we can do for you?
不必了  但千万别压我的胃
No. Just nobody press on my stomach.
还有  那条裤子你不用还了
You can keep those pants, by the way.
那是什么  那是派吗
What you got there? What is that, pie?
对  你要吃一点吗
Yeah. You want some?
切一小块给我就行了
Just cut me a little sliver.
大一点
Little bigger.
再大一点
你是害怕没派吃吗  切一大块给我
Are you afraid you're gonna run out? Cut me a real piece!